I understand that you in Russia can't
Я понимаю что вы там в России не можете
open your mouths very much because, well, you're
сильно открывать рот потому что ну вас
screwed. Yes, so I can answer you for
на бутыля Да пому я вам могу ответить за
Kadyrov and Putin because I think,
Кадырова за Путина так как я думаю как
in fact, I think I consider Kadyrov a
вот по факту Я думаю я считаю Кадырова
good
хорошим
president, the leader of his country, I
президентом лидером своей страны я его
respect him as the leader of the
уважаю вот как лидера
country. Oh, hello, where am I from and
страны о Здравствуйте Вы откуда я
where am I in St. Petersburg now? It's
а сейчас где сейчас в Питере нахожусь
funny. What are you talking about? Well, I came in to
прикольно О чём общаешься да вот зашёл
see and listen. What were
посмотреть послушать О чём
you talking about? Is it calm in St. Petersburg?
разговаривал что там в Питере у вас
Everything, everything, everything is fine. Are prices rising
спокойно Всё да Всё всё нормально цены
or
растут или
falling? What are prices rising or
опускаются что что цены растут или
falling? Yes, it seems like they were and are still the same.
опускаются Да вроде как как были так и
Well, they're rising or falling. There can't
есть Ну они поднимаются или опуска не
be any reason why they would
может быть чтобы они как были
n't fall. They were at the same
вроде и не опускаются как были на одном
level and are still the same.
уровне так и
And what should they rise? Well, I don't know,
есть А что они должны расти Ну не знаю
some kind of sanctions, sanctions, sanctions.
санкции там какие-то та санкции санкции
For you, sanctions are fairy tales. Let's
Это для вас там санкции это сказки для
say that, but everything, everything, everything is as it
вас скажем так а так всё всё всё как
was. It's funny. And what are you
было так и есть Прикольно а чём
talking about there? Well, I'm telling you, I
общаетесь ту да я же говорю я же ни о
don't talk about anything, so I came in to listen to my
чём не общаюсь так зашёл послушать своих
former, let's say, fellow countrymen. That's it.
там бывших скажем так земляков вот
a few got caught I'm in
несколько попались Я в
shock you ask incriminating questions Well,
шоке задаёшь вопросы компрометирующие Ну
to which you know the answers And all their
на которые знаешь ответы А всё у них
arguments immediately run out Oh they
аргументы заканчиваются сразу Ой
switch well yeah like those from Donbass
переключаются ну да типа эти из Донбасса
Yes, those in the occupied part they are like that
Да которые на оккупированной части они
you are
такие вы
right Well we know the truth Those who are from
правильно Ну мы знаем правду Те кто с
Donbass know the truth so yeah
Донбасса знают правду так что да
look I think so I understand that
смотрите Я думаю так что я понимаю что
you there in Russia can't
вы там в России не можете сильно
open your mouths much because well you are on a
открывать рот потому что ну вас на
bottle Yes that's why you can't
бутыля Да поэтому правду вы не можете
tell the truth but it's you Botha it's you who are afraid only
чно раска это вы Боте это вы боитесь лиш
with So why why look here you see you
с Так почему почему смотри вот видишь ты
really Yes you will never in your life say
реально Да ты никогда в жизни не скажешь
out loud there about Kadyrov yes about Putin what
вслух там про Кадырова да про Путина что
they did to Donbass Yes how they
они сделали с донбассом Да как они его
destroyed it what
уничтожили какой раньше был
Donbass used to be celebrated Euro 202 And now what have they
Донбас евро 202 праздновал А сейчас что
turned into peace in short sh Donbass Well
превратили в мира короче ш Донбасс Ну
come on Let me answer you Yes
дава Давайте я Вам отвечу Да на ваши
I can answer your question for you for Kadyrov
вопрос я вам могу ответить за Кадырова
for Putin because I think as a matter of
за Путина так как я думаю как вот по
fact I think I consider Kadyrov a good
факту Я думаю я считаю Кадырова хорошим
president the leader of his country I
президентом лидером своей страны я его
respect him as a leader
уважаю вот как лидера
countries Here is my personal opinion Who there what do they
страны Вот лично моё мнение Кто там что
think kill or not kill your own I
думат убий не убий своего
see I consider him a good leader of his
вижу я я считаю его хорошим лидером
country
своей страны
who I mean who Kadyrov so Kadyrov is
кого В смысле кого Кадырова так Кадыров
not the leader of the country Putin I mean Well the leader I
не Лидер страны Путин В смысле Ну Лидер
apologize for the slip of the tongue according to Fred not the country
извиняюсь оговорочка по фреду не страны
but the Republic Republics Republics
а Республики Республики Республики
ok yes Well ok in due time I will
хорошо да Ну хорошо в своё же время я
answer you about Putin Yes I consider
отвечу Вам по поводу Путина Да я считаю
him the leader of the country people
его лидером страны за ним идут люди его
follow him listen to him and
прислушиваются и
as if well no matter what anyone says this is my
как бы ну кто бы что не говорил это моё
personal opinion purely possibly it is
личное мнение сугубо возможно оно
wrong possibly correct here already well
неправильное возможно правильное тут уже
how to judge each in his own
ну как бы судить каждому по-своему
way Yeah And so these people Kadyrov I have
Угу А так этих людей вот Кадырова Я
always considered well a
всегда считал вот ну человеком
strong man No matter what anyone says but he is a
сильным Кто бы что не говорил но он
strong man So Well I say
сильный Так что Ну я же говорю пое
[ __ ] Look Do I understand correctly that Kadyrov
Смотри Я я правильно понимаю что Кадыров
can violate the laws of the Russian
может нарушать законы Российской
Federation because he is
Федерации потому что он
strong In what way did he violate them do you have in
сильный В чём он их нарушил у вас по
fact Well for example yes there is a fact there is a
факту есть Ну например да есть Факт есть
fact look he took a
факт смотрите он он забрал из Волгограда
Russian guy from Volgograd in short there some
русского парня короче там какой-то
guy burned the Koran in Volgograd his
парень сжёг Коран в Волгограде его там
locals there  security forces arrested Kadyrov
местные силовики арестовали Кадыров
came took him to the pre-trial detention center in Grozny and not
приехал забрал его в СИЗО Грозного а не
in Volgograd he was and then brought
в Волгограде он был да потом привёл туда
his fifteen-year-old son there and he
своего сына пятнадцатилетнего и он на
beat this
камеру избивал этого
kid on camera Yes, stop defending PP and you, this is
пацана Да защи стоп ПП и вы это же
illegal Well, how According to what law should I
незаконно Ну как По какому закону мо
do it correctly and I would have done this
правильно и сделал Я бы сам этому
guy myself, I understand correctly Yes, what in Russia,
типу я правильно понимаю Да что в России
yes Kadyrov can break the law, they beat him Yes And
да Кадыров может нарушать закон избивали
here in Russia this is already a
Да Причём здесь в России это уже момент
religious moment so once again Well, there is a law of the
религиозный так ещ раз Ну есть закон
Russian Federation where it is said What
Российской Федерации где Сказано Какое
punishment should he be, he should be
наказание он должен
judged by a Russian court Yes
его должен суд судить российский Да
Bring, for example, 5 years of
Принеси например там 5 лет лишения
imprisonment or correctional labor Yes, where in the
свободы исправительной работы да где в
legislation of the Russian Federation does it
законодательстве Российской Федерации
say that the head of the Republic
сказано что руководитель Республики
can bring his
может приводить своего
fifteen-year-old Yes, who so that he beat
пятнадцатилетнего Да который чтобы бил
this person in the pre-trial detention center on camera and
этого человека в СИЗО на камеру и
post this beating publicly Okay,
выкладывать это избиение публично Хорошо
now I will answer you, the article of the
теперь отвечу Вам статья жигани
religious Zhigani is the most correct Yes, it
религиозной это самой правильно Да она
provides for imprisonment, it does not provide for the
предусматривает Лишение свободы она не
beating of a
предусматривает избиение какими-то
person by some left-wing people Well, I honestly
левыми людьми человека Ну я честно я
agree not to deprive freedom, just give,
согласен не лишать свободу отда просто
I agree with this Well  that is yes That
вот я согласен с этим ну то есть да То
is you for breaking the law exactly the same way
есть вы за то чтобы нарушать зако точно
where there that is I understood that is
так же где там то есть я понял то есть
you just confirmed Yes that you
вы только что подтвердили Да что вы
support breaking the law of the
поддерживаете нарушение закона
Russian Federation by Kadyrov
Российской Федерации Кадыровым потому
because he is strong
что он сильный
yes you see you see you got burned because
да видишь видишь ты подгорел потому что
look when I meet everyone like
вот смотри я когда встречаю всех Таких
you I say simple facts and get
как вы я говорю простые факты и
burned because I have nothing to say I don't get
подгорает потому что нечего сказать я не
burned Goraevka
подгорают гораевка
Sva of the Russian Federation I didn't start you
Сва Российской Федерации я не начал ты
got burned And what are you justifying now you
погорел А что ты оправдываешь сейчас ты
justified I got burned you got burned because
оправ я подгорел ты подгорел потому что
look Yes you told me Are there facts
смотри Да ты сказал мне Есть ли факты
that Kadyrov broke the law I gave you the
что Кадыров нарушил закон я тебе дал
facts and you realized that you were wrong and now you
факты и ты понял что ты не прав и теперь
say that yes Well let it be so Yes I would have
говоришь что да Ну пусть будет так Да я
beaten him too I would have broken it too I give
бы тоже его побил Я бы тоже нарушил я
you a counter question a counter question
вам встречный вопрос встречный вопрос
again a counter No you already
ещё раз встречный Нет ты уже про
met about yes I put you down Yes
встречался да я тебя опустил Да потому
because you went out something Here Yes Vo got a
что ты вышел что-то Тут Да Во получил
punch in the nose in short Yes you were put in
короче удар в нос Да тебя положили в
yours yes Now you sit there, lowered,
твоё же да Ты теперь опущенный сидишь
like everything
как всё
went that's all according to the facts Great and what  you
пошёл вот и всё по фактам Здорово а чём
communicate
общаешься
Yes, it's just boring I understand I'm from the
Да так просто скучно понял Я сам из
city of Khmelnitsky Where are you from Donetsk it's cool I'm
города Хмельницкий Ты откуда я в Донецка
not in Donetsk now And
Донецке сейчас нет А
where in Russia when I arrived in
где в России когда приехал в
Russia there a week ago and what what's going on
Россию там недельку назад а что что там
there I'm sitting here bored I decided to go and
дела Вот сижу скучно решил зайти
see what's going on
посмотреть что
here you like
тут ты
me still here Russians
как я ещ тут
cap is on fire you have
русских кепка огонь у тебя
super about You burn Russians talking
супер про Ты гори русских разговариваешь
to
с
them what so what you do with
ними что так что ты так с
us what do you think why Putin is
нами как считаешь почему Путин раз
bombing
бомбит
Donbass I don't even know I can't know Well
Донбасс я не знаю даже не могу знать Ну
you're from Donbass Why Don't you
ты с Донбасса Почему Вот вы не
ask the Russians like why are they
спрашиваете у россиян типа зачем они
bombing your Donbass And what are they bombing our
бомбят ваш Донбасс А что они бомбят наш
Donbass They they Well for example they
Донбасс Они они Ну например бахмут
destroyed Bakhmut for example completely to zero so it's
уничтожили например вообще под ноль так
almost there it's being restored what will they
его так его почти его восстанавливает
restore it so they will
что будут восстанавливать его так будут
restore and who will stop the people
восстанавливать а людей кто остановит
70,000 people who will
70.000 людей кто там
restore there stupidly Ruins so stupidly
восстановит там тупо Руины так тупо
Ruins Well I understand Well well well did you
Руины Ну понятно Ну ну ну вы что там
also participate there what-what did you also
тоже участвовали что-что вы что тоже там
participate there if Russia hadn't attacked then in
участвовали если бы Россия не напала то
short there wouldn't have been  Bakhmut destroyed so Well of
короче не было бахмута уничтоженного так
course Mariupol also because of you same as
Ну конечно Мариуполь тоже из-за вас же
Mariupol so Mariupol also like has not been
что и Мариуполь так Мариуполь также типа
restored to this day look people
не восстановили до сих пор вон люди до
still Mitin Maul Mariupol already
сих пор Митин мауль Мариуполь уже
Mariupol is already completely restored
Мариуполь уже полностью восстановлен
look five houses built everything look at the
смотри пять домов построили всё посмотри
rallies of people in Mariupol who what they
митинги людей в Мариуполе которые что им
promised that they were building apartments and there are still none
обещали что строят квартиры и нету до
I was there a month ago in
сих пор я там месяц назад был в
Mariupol look in short firstly
Мариуполе посмотри вот короче во-первых
most of the residents of Mariupol are simply
большинство жителей Мариуполя просто
gone they either died or left
нету они либо погиб либо уехали
from there I know a lot of people from Mariupol yes those
оттуда вот я кучу народу из Мариуполя
who left under the occupation did not
знаю да которые уехали под оккупации не
remain that's one and secondly Even those who were
остались это раз а вовторых Даже те что
left without apartments Yes that's how many like there are that
остались без квартир Да вот сколько типа
they still live in destroyed apartments
есть что они в разбитых квартирах до сих
Well I don't know Mariupol is
пор живут Ну я не знаю Мариуполь
normal
нормально
there Why are you
там Зачем ты
building everything there how many houses have been built
там всё строи сколько там домов
there everything has been
построили там весь по
restored with How many houses What was the
восстановили с Сколько домов Сколько
population of Mariupol do you
население Мариуполя было
remember I don't remember half a million I was there for the
помнишь не помню полмиллиона я я там
first time a month There was a population of half a million
первый раз вот был месяц На полмиллиона
in Mariupol how many
в Мариуполе было население сколько это
houses are needed  rebuild
домов нужно отстроить
Well, they rebuilt far away, they rebuilt, come and
Ну даль
see,
отстроили отстроили ты приедь посмотри
and how is your city there? They don't shoot at you,
а у вас там как город Не стреляют тебя
I'm asking Look, you destroyed
спрашиваю Смотри вот вы да уничтожили
half a million people, how much did you rebuild?
полмиллиона город сколько вы отстроили
Almost everything there was immediately
Да почти всё там сразу моментально его
rebuilt. So how much did you
начали отстраивать Так сколько
rebuild, well, they definitely rebuilt the greater half
отстроили ну большую половину точно
250,000 people to resettle, yeah Well,
отстроили 250.000 человек расселить да
somewhere like that, yeah, can you imagine
Ну где-то так да ты представляешь
how many
сколько это
houses that is? Well, that's not it. Let's see
домов Ну это не до Давай посмотрим
250,000 people Let's say a family of three,
250.000 человек Пусть семья из трёх
yeah, everyone there is a mom, dad, and a child, on
человек да всё там мама папа и ребёнок в
average, the EU has someone Living alone, someone
среднем ЕС кто-то Одинокий живёт кто-то
four. Let's say out of three people, that's
четвер Да пусть из трёх человек это
80,000 families, if in
получается семей э 80.000 семей если в
one entrance in a nine-story building, for example, a
одном подъезде в девятиэтажке например
nine-story building, in one entrance there are
девятиэтажный дом в одном подъезде
four apartments - that's 36 apartments.
четыре квартиры - это 36 квартир Да
Let's see 84. Yes,
давай смотрим 84 Да
84,000 apartments, 36 each. Let's
84.000 квартир по 36 Давай сейчас
see now how many houses that should be, in
посмотрим сколько это домов должно быть
short, damn, 2,500 houses, it seems. Let's see
это короче блин 2500 домов походу будет
84,000 And what 84 again so let's do it
84.000 А что 84 ещё раз так давай ещё
again 250,000 people Yes it was divided by
раз 250.000 людей Да было разделили на
three yes 80 and 83 84,000 what 83 turns out
три да 80 а 83 84.000 че 83 получается
yes we divide it 83,000 apartments
да делим это 83000 квартир
83,333 apartments we divide by in the train kti this
83333 квартиры делим на в поезде кти это
means
значит
now
сечас
divide 36 Yes there should be
разделить 36 Да должно
2,314 entrances That is, if we divide in in the
2314 подъездов То есть если разделим в в
house let there be five entrances Yes,
доме пусть пять подъездов Да пяти
even a five-entrance house yes this is necessary 400 500
подъездный дом даже да это надо 400 500
houses
домов
to build Mariupol this is all stars just
отстроить Мариуполь это всё звезд просто
stars 505 entrance houses
звезд 505 подъездных домов
and where are you
а где ты
sitting Agree you'll bring something together really no no
сидишь Согласись что-то сведёшь правда
I'm telling you what they
нет нет я те говорю что
built how much they built well how many
отстроили сколько отстроили ну сколько
houses they built half half they
домов построили половину половину
built Listen, damn, in Rostov, in
отстроили Слушай у вас блин в Ростове в
Krasnodar, in Moscow so many are not being built in
Краснодаре в Москве столько не строится
short houses like Mariupol as soon as
короче домов так Мариуполь сразу его как
they took it they immediately started building how many So
забрали его сразу начали строить сколько
how many they built It's physically
Так сколько отстроили Физически
impossible only so immediately count the houses e
невозможно лько так сразу считаю дома е
Let's see now How many houses did
Давай посмотрим сейчас Сколько домов
they build in
отстроили она в
Mariupol And where are you sitting wait Now
Мариуполе А где ты сидишь подожди Сейчас
we'll see Something like this Oh finally in the twenty-
мы посмотрим Типа так О наконец двадцать
second year 19 houses were put into operation in the
второго года было введено 19 домов в
twenty-third year 33
двадцать третьем году 33
houses that is look 33 houses in the twenty-
дома то есть смотри 33 дома в двадцать
third year Yes,
третьем году Да вот
in short, here Oh now here he writes in
короче вот Ой сейчас вот пишет в
Mariupol at the end of the twenty-
Мариуполе вот на конец двадцать
fourth year yes that is for d2 tre d
четвёртого года да то есть за д2 тре д
four almost 70 apartment buildings were built in Mariupol
чет в Мариуполе построено почти 70
Well they built 70 houses anyway once again
домов Ну отстроили всё равно 70 домов
70 houses
ещё раз 70 домов
Yes for a couple of entrances Yes, oh my where did you
Да на пару подъездов Да ё-моё куда
run off to
убежал
Hello Hello Where are you from Well
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Вы откуда Да
from Krasnodar Cool And what is your
ну с Краснодара Прикольно А что у вас
uniform so
форма такая
interesting it's just a special uniform posing
интересная это просто спецовка позирует
in Russian military
в Российской военной
clothing Well, yes, I got it the model in short
одежде Ну да понял модель короче ну
what was in the store I bought one why
какая была в магазине такую купил почему
not And now this is where you are
бы нет А сейчас это где вы находитесь у
you have a workshop basement bomb
вас мастерская подвал бомба
shelter at a construction site I am
убежище на строительном объекте нахожусь
cool What do you talk about
прикольно О чём общаетесь
Builder In all sorts of ways
Строитель Да по-всякому
with Ukrainians mainly about
с украинцами в основном о
war super quite an interesting topic How do
войне супер довольно интересная тема Как
you rate that  in the fourth year of this
вы оцениваете что на четвёртый год этой
full-scale war if we count yes
войны полномасштабной если считать да
Or as if already if we count from the fourteenth
Или как бы уже если с четырнадцатого
year then already for the
года считать то уже на о
year Ukrainian drones and missiles have been
год украинские беспилотники и ракеты
flying into the territory of the Russian
прилетают территории Российской
Federation By the way, you have a VTU of
Федерации у Вас кстати втус
Krasnodar Krai the day before yesterday or Poza the day
Краснодарского края позавчера или Поза
before yesterday a new Ukrainian this
позавчера новая украинская вот эта
missile long Neptune flew into the
ракета длинный Нептун прилетело по
oil depot It is quite possible I dont know what
нефтебазе вполне возможно не знаю что
flew in but something flew in yes yes it still
прилетело но чтото прилетело да да до
seems to be burning
сих пор вроде горит
Yes I have no idea even how it
Да без понятия не знаю даже то Как так
turns out that Russia wanted Kyiv there in
получается что Россия хотела там Киев за
3 days and now its being cut off on its own
3 дня а теперь отре на своей
territory I know and about Kyiv in 3 days I
территории знаю а про Киев за 3 дня я
hear exclusively from Ukrainians
слышу исключительно только от украинцев
no no maybe look va no dont look
нет нет може посмотреть ва нет не смотри
all your propagandists Skobeev and so
ваши все пропагандисты скобееве и так
on Yes they said well take Kyiv in 3 days
дальше Да говорили Киев возьмём за 3 дня
and so on now everyone has shut up Well come on
и так дальше теперь все заткнулись Ну ну
tell me I give you
рассказывайте
permission No need to give me permission Ill
разрешаю Да не надо мне разрешать Я сам
decide for myself what Ill decide Ill decide for myself what to
решу что я реша я сам решу что мне
do No need to
делать Не нужно тут дешёвыми
put it higher here with cheap manipulations come on we have
манипуляциями поставить выше давай мы
nt talked to you yet
ещё с вами не беседовали
to find out Who has what
чтобы выяснить У кого какой
intelligence if you have questions about 3 days well
интеллект если у вас вопросы по 3 дня ну
you can contact skabeeva and ask her this
можете обратиться к скабеевой и ей этот
question about 3 days Okay I did
вопрос задать по поводу 3 дня Хорошо я
n't talk about days and refer refer
про дня не говорил и сослаться сослаться
to official sources Yes General
на официальные источники Да генерального
Staff Or something you can't this is
штаба Или что-то вы не можете это
provost with Shea
провост с Шей
and now otte on your territory
а теперь отте по своей территории
boy
мальчик
Tell me Show me an official
Расскажи Покажите мне официальное
statement that the task was to
утверждение того что ставилась задача
capture Kyiv are you really or
захватить Киев ты реально или
what
что
document statement of the General
документ заявление генерального
Staff I understand correctly that your troops
штаба правильно понимаю что ваши войска
just like decided to take a walk near
просто так типа решили прогуляться возле
Kyiv yes
Киева да
most likely you don't have a very
скорее всего у вас интеллект не очень
high intelligence you Yes my low intelligence
высокий вы Да мой невысокий интеллект
understands that here you are like this
так и понимает что вот вам вот
from the Russian Federation Putin
таким из Российской Федерации Путин
says so now we will advance
говорит так сейчас мы продвинется
into a pile of dead equipment How did it
в кучу техники дохлых Как же так
happen
получилось
what kind of like
каких таких как
you well our conversation is filled with
вы ну наполняется нашу беседу
emotional I fill our conversation with
эмоциональными Я наполняю нашу беседу
emotional expressions Yes and
эмоциональными выражениями Да и
humiliation of
унижением
you yes yes more emotions more emotions
вас да да эмоций побольше эмоций
Yes you you
побольше Да вы вы
Russians attacked Ukraine here is a document for you
россияне напали на Украину вот вам
Hello Dava let's have a normal
Здравствуйте Дава давайте нормально
conversation I'm not arguing
пообщаемся Я не ссорюсь
I'm not either I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky  Where are you
я тоже не Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
from Belgorod from Belgorod itself
откуда из Белгорода из самого Белгорода
or from the
или из
region of Belgorod itself from the region
области самого Белгорода с области это
you are in a hostel
вы в общаге
somewhere And in a hostel there is no house in the kitchen And
где-то А в общаге нет дома на кухне А
what are you building at home it's
что вас строишь дома
already Friday gathered to sit down for tea
уже пятница собрались посидеть на чай
Pite how old are you and let's
Пите по сколько вам лет й
drink Well 18 I understand who you study or
пьём Ну по 18 понял на кого учитесь или
work as then the card number will go Yes
работаете потом номер карточки пойдёт Да
not just those well yes In what
не просто те ну да В какой
field I am in the field of logistics they are in the field of the
сфере Я в сфере логистики они в сфере
Ministry of Emergency Situations I understood about the Ministry of Emergency Situations now there is
МЧС понял о мчсника сейчас работы
enough work in Belgorod yes Yes
хватает в Белгороде да
not people in general like work
не люди вообще типа работы
not everyone is resting constantly something will either
не все отдыхают постоянно что-то или
fly in or burn
прилетит или сгорит
Yes very rarely flies in more often flies
Да очень редко прилетает чаще прилетает
to Kharkov
в Харьков
Yes Listen and here is such an interesting question What do
Да Слушай а вот такой интересный вопрос
you think has your life become better because of the war
Как вы считаете вам лучше жить от войны
or
стало или
worse better I think yes yes good m
хуже получше я думаю да да хоро м у
interesting I like
интересны Мне нравится
that everything has become better for you they are
что вам лучше
bombing Ukraine well look let's
бомбят ну так смотри давай нормально
try to talk normally I'm asking you
попробуем поговори Я же тебя спрашиваю
yes how has your life become
да чем тебе стало жить
better a second literally I'll open
лучше секунду буквально я открою
wait in short import substitution is underway
погоди короче идёт импортозамещение
you understand that is
понимаешь
at  we are becoming our own
то есть у нас становится всё своё
Russian we are generally
русская мы вообще
military what kind of military man are you God look
военные какой ты военный Боже посмотри
at yourself
на себя
Child military man this one What is in front Yes you
Дитё военный вот этот Что спереди Да он
can see he is sharp he is a sportsman he can
видно он чёткий он спортик онто может
be Military man and at most you in short carry chalk at
быть Военным а ты максимум короче в
school In short you will help teachers
школе мел таскать Короче будешь учителям
military military men I have a message
военны военные наме
for That's it look I am
ла за Вот то смотрите я же серьёзно
asking seriously here lived Belgorod everything is calm
спрашиваю вот жил Белгород все спокойно
yes And now something is wrong people in
да А сейчас что-то не так то люди в
Belgorod live better or worse from this
Белгороде живут лучше или хуже от этой
war it is clear that it is worse well
войны понятно что хуже как бы ну всё
anyway there is a probability any yes it turns
равно есть вероятность любая да то
out If they began to live worse Why do
получается Если стали жить хуже Да зачем
you need Belgorod listen there this one I am looking at
вам Белгород во слушай там этот я смотрю
So wait What is your name that one
Во так подожди Тебя как зовут тот Что
sitting in front What is your
спереди сидит Как тебя
name Danil Danil me Andrey listen
зовут Данил Данил меня Андрей слушай
you don't need to open a window And this one who is waving
тебе не окно надо открыть А это вывести
there in short his sweaters from a
который там машет короче свои кофти от
mute we will talk
немы с тобой пообщаемся
normally this is
нормально это
for the people of Belgorod then it is
для людям Белгорода тогда это
war You understand that the people of Belgorod do
война Ты понимаешь что люди Белгорода
not decide this at all that is they do not
это никак не решают вообще то есть им
need it
она не нужна
Yes even if it was needed Who would
Да даже если была нужна Кто бы кого
listen to whom so in the whole world now not
послушал так во всём мире сейчас не
only absolutely anyone  he will start and come
только абсолютно любой начнёт и придёт
as the president decides so everything is clear the matter is
как решит президент так всё понятно дело
you all had presidential elections and you
у вас были выборы президента и вы его
elected him the last time he said I
выбрали вот в последний раз он говорил Я
want Continue who are you Well I don't know the
хочу Продолжи кого вы Ну я не знаю того
president who would say that there is no
президента который бы говорил что не
need for
надо
war there is no need for war they will come they will give it to us as they
войны не надо войны придут дадут нам так
came out and stood on their border and
как вот вышли и Встали на свою границу и
everything so that no one would come to you
всё чтобы никто к вам не
Yes and guarantees I need ranti
пришёл Да а гарантии Мне нужны ранти
what guarantees look you lived
какие гарантии смотри вы жили вообще
generally calmly not at all Kharkov went to
спокойно вообще нел Харьков ездил
buy whatever you want on Barabashova Yes and
покупать на Барабашова всё что хочешь Да
now you are afraid that some
а а теперь Боитесь чтобы какие-то
guarantees are not guarantees you have nuclear
гарантии не гарантии у вас ядерное
weapons what guarantees do you need Are you
оружие есть какие вам гарантии нужны Вы
kidding
что прикалываетесь
for a long time in short the outcome is one that as the
давно короче исход один что как реши
president decides so it will be why he was
президент так оно всё и будет почему его
elected because there are other adequate
избрали потому что других адекват
presidents so it will be of
президент так оно и будет
course of course that is the population of the
так конечно конечно то есть население
Russian Federation and you too will accept
Российской Федерации и вы тоже примете
any decision of the president
любое решение президента
So naturally Well if the president of the
Так естественно Хорошо если президент
Russian Federation decides to
Российской Федерации примет решение
give the Belgorod region to Ukraine you will
отдать Белгородскую область Украине вы
accept it no for
примете нетт
example they decided something with Trump
например что-то они с трампом порешали
Yes for example he says and they decided Crimea
Да например он говорит и решили Крым
goes to Russia and the Belgorod region to
уходит России а Белгородская область
Ukraine for example
Украине например
Yeah here you are together with  together the
Ага вот вас вместе с областью вместе
region together with you will be given to Ukraine Well, there will be
область вместе с вами отдадут Украине Ну
some Well, that is, you will accept
какие-то Ну то есть вы вы примете
this decision of Putin yes I
этот решение Путина да
mean no
В смысле не
Where no Where will you go you no well the
Куда нене Куда вы выйдете вас не ну
territory will be handed over together with the
территорию передадут вместе с
serfs this has always been the principle I
крепостными это же такой принцип был
mean with the serfs Well, everyone will
всегда В смысле с крепостными Ну все
just pack their things and leave No, no
просто соберут вещи и уедут Нет нет
one will say that this is the territory of Ukraine
никого что сказа это территория Украины
Yes Belgorod region everyone who lives there Yes, it is
Да Белгородская область все кто вот там
you, you will be Zelensky's subjects and not
вы вы подданные Зеленского будете а не
subjects
подданные
you will be Zelensky's subjects not
вы будете подданными Зеленского не
subjects why Well, yes, look, the first
подданными почему Ну да смотри первая
first news, the first news that they
первая новость первая новость что
will hand over things in a suitcase in Ukraine
передадут в Украине вещи в чемодан
Moscow Magadan and not things in a suitcase and the
Москва Магадан а не вещи в чемодан а
border of the Belgorod region with Bryansk
граница Белгородской области с Брянской
Oryol with Kursk is already closed everything is
Орловской с Курской уже закрыто всё
worth bast shoes Aladino in short from the regiment and no
стоит лапти аладино короче из полка и
one will be a thief in life Well,
никого не пу ниг в жизни не будет Ну а
why but imagine Well, imagine
почему а вот представ Ну представьте
Trump will agree Yes in short,
Трамп договорится Да короче
take it like together with the wife well wait come on
так забрать типа вместе с жи ну подожди
Okay, look that is Okay,
давай Хорошо смотри то есть Хорошо
look now we imagine such a situation
смотри вот сейчас такую ситуацию
Here they are agreeing all the way to
представляем Вот договариваются они до
Kyiv  territory to submit to Russia
самого Киева территорию подать России
well they will close all borders Where
хорошо закроют все границы Куда люди
will people go everyone will remain Well it works If they
денутся все останутся Ну получается Если
close Yes they will grab us here and that's it and we will
закроют Да нас тут схватят и всё и мы
end up in Russia it's terrible now people are terrible
попадём в Россию это ужас сечас люди ужа
but look the trick is not the trick is you
но смотри Фишка в то не Фишка в том
understand it's not Zelensky who decides for
понимаешь у нас не Зеленский решает у
us it's the people who decide through their own
нас решает народ через своих
and wait through their deputies and through their
и подожди через своих депутатов и через
these presidents And if you
своих этих президентов А если ты
say that you will make any decision
говоришь что вы примете любое решение
as Putin decides look yes
как Путин решит смотри у нас да
Zelensky deputies they rely on the
Зеленский депутаты они опираются на
opinion of the people Yes he can't just take and
мнение народа Да он не может взять и
sign sign like I'll give in short the
подписать подписать типа я отдам короче
region We are like Okay Zelensky
области Мы такие Окей Зеленский так
decided so we don't have this we have that People are
решил у нас этого нет у нас та Люди
against for example this And you get it
против например такого А у вас
If if Putin decided there
получается Если если Путин решил чит
will be a cheat that is you completely give
будет то есть вы полностью отдаёте
power over yourself to Putin Okay you
власть над собой Путину Хорошо
can Why
можно Почему в переговорах переваривают
only Putin and Trump are digested in negotiations Why Zelensky their
только Путин и Трамп Почему Зеленский их
Casa is not there look No just the opposite
Каса нет смотри Нет как раз наоборот
look Putin with Trump Trump has never met with Putin
смотри Путин с трампом Трамп с Путиным
but he
не встречался ни разу а Зеленским
met with Zelensky once look Trump and Zelensky
встречался раз смотри Трамп с Зеленским
just met
как раз встречались
not  met who met on the way like this
не встречался кто встречался с пути вот
look here this Zelensky kicked
так вот смотри вот вот это Зеленский
him out of the White House Come on
пинком его выгнали Белого дома Давай
let's talk Well look who talked to Putin
давай пообщаемся Ну смотри кто с Путиным
Trump didn't talk Zelensky didn't
общался Трамп не общался Зеленский не
talk Zelensky was thrown out right
общался Зеленского выкинули правильно
again Look who talked to Putin
ещё раз Смотри кто с Путиным общался с
Putin doesn't even want to talk Trump Talk where
Путиным даже не хочет Трамп Общаться где
Well where is Trump or Zelensky No one
А ну где Трамп или Зеленский Никто с
negotiated with Putin no one
Путиным переговоры не вёл он никому не
needs him Well I'm telling you Zelensky
нужен Ну так я тебе говорю Зеленского
was kicked out of the White House again look no
вынули с Белого дома ещё раз смотри с
one even wants to
Путиным никто не хочет даже
talk to Putin She's a type
разговаривать Она
Well you see
вид Ну видишь
everything like pipska comment subscribe to my
всё лайк пиписка комент пидпишить на мий
Telegram right now axis win a
Telegram прямо зараз ось вин а
Popik this is very and very important YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through scarg Orcs in the shadows ban
загоняя нас через скарг Орки в теней бан
and very many videos are not shown to people
и дуже багато видео не показуе людям
at times are not shown information about streams
вчасно не показуе информация про стрими
That is why in order for me Mali operational
Тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
links are written right behind a  Popik there in
звязок пишиться прямо за а Попик там в
telegrams okrim video tezh tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you to
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
keep constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава украини пись